<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!--
   New Perspectives on XML 3rd Edition
   Tutorial 6
   Review Assignment

   Harpe Gaming Store Board Game Reviews

   Filename:         game_reviews.xml
   Supporting Files:

-->

<reviews>
   <review gid="bg210" revid="r803">
      <summary>
         <h3>Highly Recommended</h3>
         <p><i>Towers and Temples</i> is a great game. The balance is just about perfect and
         each player must carefully choose roles each turn. Even though the strategic
         possibilities are nearly endless, the game is simple to learn. The replay value is high
         and gets even better when you replace some of the cards with new cards available
         in the expansion packs.</p>
         <p>Rating: 4.5 / 5</p>
      </summary>
   </review>
   <review gid="bg210" revid="r804">
      <summary>
         <h3>Great Strategic Board Game</h3>
         <p>We tested <i>Towers and Temples</i> with everything from 2 player to 6 players and we can
         strongly recommend the game. The different phases of the game  are interesting and intriguing,
         from bluffing and stealing to site construction and planning. With the variety of cards
         and scenarios, no two games are ever quite the same. It's a great introduction to the world
         of strategic board games and role playing.</p>
         <p>Rating: 5 / 5 </p>
      </summary>
   </review>
   <review gid="bg210" revid="r805">
      <summary>
         <h3>An Incredible Game</h3>
         <p>The artwork in the cards and for the board is excellent and one of the best around.
         As for play, this game offers lots of strategy, and there are tough decisions to make every turn.
         It's not only important to select the character that increases your chances for scoring, but also
         to anticipate the characters the opponents are likely to select, and then hedge against their
         availability. This causes a lot of unpredictability and deep strategic thinking. However, it
         can still be played at a more basic level for younger users.</p>
         <p>We had a lot of fun with this game and rate it as "Best in its Class". Highly
         recommended.</p>
         <p>Rating: 10 / 10</p>
      </summary>
   </review>
   <review gid="bg211" revid="r803">
      <summary>
         <h3>Tedious and Confusing</h3>
         <p>The list of war simulation games is long. All of them share similar features including
         the formation of temporary Alliance and battles simulated through random draws of a deck
         or the roll of the die. <i>Alliance</i> offers very little that is new or innovative
         in that regard.
         </p>
         <p>We found that gameplay itself to be too drawn-out and confusing. In fact, I dare say we
         spent more time reading and rereading the rule book than actually playing the game.
         If you want to read a book on war, we suggest Sun Tzu.</p>
         <p>Rating: 1 / 5</p>
      </summary>
   </review>
   <review gid="bg211" revid="r805">
      <summary>
         <h3>Decent Game but Many are Better</h3>
         <p><i>Alliance</i> is a good war simulation game. We found the game play to be robust
         and engaging. The rules are long and drawn out, but for anyone with experience in
         this class of board games, there is little there that's unexpected or difficult.
         We think the battle simulation cards are some of the best we have encountered.
         </p>
         <p>All of that being said, the competition for this type of game is fierce. There are
         a lot of established titles with loyal clients. We're not exactly sure where
         <i>Alliance</i> fits in with that group. It's a good game, but not good enough
         to draw our attention away from games like <i>Battle Tested</i> and <i>Global
         Conflict</i>.</p>
         <p>Rating: 7 / 10</p>
      </summary>
   </review>
   <review gid="bg211" revid="r806">
      <summary>
         <h3>Fun and Challenging</h3>
         <p><i>Alliance</i> is fun game and is sure to appeal to war
         game enthusiasts. We think it offers several new ideas that
         we're surprised have not been utilized in other simulation
         games. The card system
         and the investment options give the game a "real world" feel.</p>
         <p>Things we liked:</p>
         <ul>
            <li>Variety of Battle Scenarios</li>
            <li>Flexible Rules and Setup</li>
            <li>Detail and Historical Accuracy</li>
            <li>Wealth of Expansion Packs</li>
         </ul>
         <p>Things we hated:</p>
         <ul>
            <li>Long and Complicated Rule Book</li>
            <li>Setup takes too Long</li>
         </ul>
         <p>This is a great game for anyone 16 years or older. Younger
         players may have trouble with the rules and may be bored</p>
         <p>Rating: 4 / 5 </p>
      </summary>
   </review>

</reviews>
