<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!--
   New Perspectives on XML 3rd Edition
   Tutorial 6
   Review Assignment

   Harpe Gaming Store Board Games
   Author:
   Date:

   Filename:         games.xml
   Supporting Files: games.xsl

-->

<games>
   <game gid="bg210">
      <title>Towers and Temples</title>
      <manufacturer>Royal Games</manufacturer>
      <price>17.73</price>
      <releaseDate>10/21/2017</releaseDate>
      <media>Board Game</media>
      <age>10+</age>
      <players>2 - 8</players>
      <time>30 - 60 minutes</time>
      <image>bg210.png</image>

      <summary>
         <h3>Rule an Ancient City</h3>
         <p><i>Towers and Temples</i> is the winner of the 2016 Palmer Medal for
         Best New Simulation Board Game. Players adopt role cards of characters
         from ancient Greece and Rome in an attempt to manage the administration of
         a city. Each role provides a different ability and strategy. However, one
         role card belongs to a deadly assassin and players must be constantly
         aware of betrayal and double-cross. This card game provides a ton of enjoyment
         and can handle up to seven players and expansion packs available for
         larger parties.</p>
         <p>This is a nicely balanced game, where each player must carefully choose
         his or her roles and the strategies can quickly change with the turn of a card.
         However the level of randomness is just right and cunning and resourcefulness
         can overcome bad luck (if given time.) I do not recommend this game unless
         there are at least 4 players; less than that reduces the intrigue and some
         of the game appeal.</p>
      </summary>
      <scores>
         <score category="Entertainment">8</score>
         <score category="Strategy">9</score>
         <score category="Innovation">7</score>
         <score category="Art Work">6</score>
         <score category="Community Enjoyment">10</score>
         <score category="Ease of Set Up">9</score>
         <score category="Play Again">10</score>
      </scores>
   </game>
   <game gid="bg211">
      <title>Alliance</title>
      <manufacturer>Bearnes Brothers</manufacturer>
      <price>22.15</price>
      <releaseDate>9/14/2017</releaseDate>
      <media>Board Game</media>
      <age>12+</age>
      <players>2 - 6</players>
      <time>60 - 120 minutes</time>
      <image>bg211.png</image>

      <summary>
         <h3>Decide the Fate of the World</h3>
         <p>The world is at war. <i>Alliance</i> challenges you and your opponents to
         decide the outcome. As one of the world powers battling for supremacy you must
         lead your country's military drive; but you can't do it alone. You have to form
         alliances and then betray your allies before they betray you!</p>
         <p>Decide where to strike, when to strike and the intensity of the strike. Will
         it be a bombing raid, an offshore missile barrage, or an invasion with land forces
         and tanks? Plan your attack, move into enemy territory with your forces and
         win the conflict.</p>
         <p>The economic destiny of your nation is also at stake. Buy armaments and develop
         secret weapons from your country's economic funds and natural reserves; but be
         sure to save something for the future.</p>
      </summary>
      <scores>
         <score category="Entertainment">7</score>
         <score category="Strategy">10</score>
         <score category="Innovation">6</score>
         <score category="Art Work">5</score>
         <score category="Community Enjoyment">8</score>
         <score category="Ease of Set Up">7</score>
         <score category="Play Again">5</score>
      </scores>
   </game>
</games>
